TASNIM HASAN RIFAT

WEB DESIGNER & WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Hi! My name is Tasnim Hasan Rifat. I am a Web Developer, and I'm very passionate and dedicated to my work. With O2 years experience as a professional Web developer. I have acquired the skills and knowledge necessary to make your project a success. I enjoy every step of the design process, from discussion and collaboration to concept and execution, but I find the most satisfaction in seeing the finished product do everything for you that it was created to do.

CONTACT

+8801759607553 Baridhara J Block, Dhaka 1212 tasnmhasan@gmail.com www.tasnimhasan.com

PERSONAL SKILLS

- Define the problem, challenge, or opportunity.
- Attentive & Versatile
- Good Communication
- Multi-tasking

LANGUANGES

English • • • • • Bengali

EDUCATION

Independent University, Bangladesh • 2018-Current

Bsc In Computer Science & Engineering

Al Amin Academy School & College, Chandpur • 2017

Higher Secondary Certificate(HSC)

Al Amin Academy School & College, Chandpur • 2015

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

EXPERIENCE

Fiverr & Upwork, 2017 - Current

Web Designer & WordPress Developer

Fiverr, 2018 - Current

Graphic Designer

SKILLS

SKILLS	
Web Design	••••
WordPress	••••
javascript	••••
C++	••••
PHP	•••
Photoshop	• • • •
Illustrator	••••
Microsoft Office	••••